1. ركب الحافلة عند 7 صباحا.
(he got on the bus at 7 AM)
2. مشى إلى المدرسة.
(he walked to the school)
3. صعد الدّرج.
(he went upstairs)
4. نزل من الدّرج.
(he went downstairs)
5. تسلّق الجبل.
(he climbed the mountain)
6. سلّم على جاره.
(he greeted his neighbor)
7. سأل سؤالا.
(he asked a question)
8. أجاب على السّؤال.
(he answered the question)
9. حلّ المشكل.
(he solved the problem)
10. نظر إلى السّماء.
(he looked up to the sky)
11. شاهد المبارات.
(he watched the match)
12. وقف في الصّفّ.
(he stood in the queue)
13. انتظر دوره.
(he waited for his turn)
14. سمع صوتا.
(he heared a sound)
15. انصت إلى كلام جده.
(he listened to the Talk of his grandpa)
16. كلّم معلّم العربيّة.
(he talked to the Arabic teacher)
17. بنى البناء البيت.
(the builder built the house)
18. أصلح الحاسوب.
(he repaired the computer)
19. ملأ الفراغ.
(he filled in the blank)
20. أنهى عمله.
(he finished his work)
21. قطع الورقة بالمقص.
(he cut the paper with the ceaser)
22. جلس على الكرسيّ.
(he sat on the chair)
23. استلقى على السرير.
(he laid down on the bed)
24. كسر ساقه.
(he broke his leg)
25. مرض الكلب.
(the dog got sick)